♪♪
♪ I get up, and
nothing gets me down ♪
♪ You got it tough, I've
seen the toughest around ♪
♪ And I know, baby,
just how you feel ♪
♪ You've got to roll with the
punches to get to what's real ♪
♪ Oh, can't you see
me standing here ♪
♪ I've got my back against
the record machine ♪
♪ I ain't the worst
that you've seen ♪
♪ Oh, can't you
see what I mean ♪
♪ Might as well jump, jump ♪
♪ Might as well jump ♪
♪ Go ahead and jump, jump ♪
♪ Go ahead and jump ♪
♪ Hey, you, who said that ♪
♪ Baby, how you been ♪
♪ You say you don't know ♪
♪ You won't know
until you begin ♪
♪ Oh, can't you see
me standing here ♪
♪ I've got my back against
the record machine ♪
♪ I ain't the worst
that you've seen ♪
♪ Oh, can't you
see what I mean ♪
♪ Might as well jump, jump ♪
♪ Go ahead and jump ♪
♪ Jump ♪
♪ Ohhh ♪
♪ Might as well jump, jump ♪
♪ Go ahead and jump ♪
♪ Get it and jump, jump ♪
♪ Jump ♪
♪♪